The rules keep changing.
I've been rehearsing every possible outcome.
Once this thought arises, there is no more room for right or wrong.
I am resolved to sever this flood
so that my soul can break free from mediocrity,
from loneliness and distinction.
One more step and you'll fall into madness.
Don't fall down.
I look towards the top.
Chase !
Refined to perfection.
Never retreat, no matter the danger.
I dare to defy the heavens !
Always overcome the obstacles,
ignite the seas with blood,
bloom through trials and tribulations.
Even the sharpest thorns
will be reduced into ashes.
What is there to fear ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Southern Domain\NAllheaven Star System
So that's why my Origin Soul guided me here...
There's a thunder planet hidden here !
Since my physical body has collapsed
and my Origin Soul was damaged,
I need a place with abundant thunder energy in order to heal.
This place
is perfect.
Why did the Celestial Guard stop here ?
This place
must hide something else.
I'll leave the Celestial Guard here
and investigate on my own.
The thunder here is pure.
It's very similar to my Thunder Origin Soul.
The might of this thunder
is in fact
an opportunity for me.
I will use this thunder
to heal my Origin Soul.
He's devouring heavenly thunder ?
The fiend is getting more and more terrifying !
At this rate
when will I ever be free !?
10 years later
In just 10 years,
my Origin Soul has completely recovered.
While healing my Origin Soul,
I absorbed a massive amount of thunder energy.
The density of the thunder energy still hasn't diminished.
I might as well continue
and use the thunder again
to reforge my physical body !
Although the avatar can't practice Ancient God techniques,
it can still use the Ancient God Tactic
to absorb the energy of the heavens and the earth
and reforge my body.
Thunder...
gather !
The last time I had to reforge a physical body
was back in the Land of the Ancient God
when I barely escaped Tuo Sen alive.
It's already been hundreds of years...
I traveled from Suzaku to Allheaven
and was careful at every step.
But I still ended up losing my physical body...
And this time,
I slept for a full 60 years.
60 years later
After 60 years,
I drained all the thunder energy of this planet
with the Ancient God Tactic
to reforge my physical body.
This body
is imbued with thunder energy.
One could say that...
the Dao can't get rid of me anymore.
My new body is complete.
Now it's time for the Heaven Defying Bead to absorb the Moongazer Serpent's bone
and finally be complete.
The Moongazer Serpent's bone is enormous
so the Heaven Defying Bead is absorbing it slowly.
Might as well use this opportunity
to review what I gained on this trip.
To steal the Moongazer Serpent's bone,
I used a large number of my artifacts.
These artifacts I got from Greed
are an unexpected gain.
The soul of a Celestial Mountain is sealed inside this mountain.
Extracting souls of mountains,
rivers,
and even planets,
and then wielding those souls to attack
is something only second step cultivators can do.
In Greed's hands, this mountain
was enough to cut through the Moongazer Serpent.
Now that Greed's Divine Sense has been removed,
I'm sure I'll find some uses for it
when facing enemies.
What a pity...
With my current strength, I can barely control it.
But as long as I have this artifact,
it will allow me to comprehend this spell unique to the second step
ahead of time.
This object is not the true Mountains and Rivers Painting.
Rather, it relies on a spell
to imprint the Mountains and Rivers Dao onto the painting.
Although it's a fake,
it was enough to withstand the Moongazer Serpent's attacks.
It's an excellent defensive artifact.
Unfortunately, this object
was damaged by the Ancient God's finger.
If I get the chance,
I'll definitely try to repair it.
This looks just like an ordinary mortal emperor's crown,
nothing about it is particularly remarkable.
But it faced the Ancient God's finger head on
without even being damaged.
This is no ordinary item.
These 5 gems
contain the 5 elements.
This energy isn't very strong.
It felt like it was looking for something on me.
Maybe...
Red Butterfly of planet Suzaku
had a Five Elements body.
Could this object be related to her ?
Greed also said that
he used the souls of 9999 mortal emperors
in order to control this artifact.
Perhaps only an emperor with a Five Elements body
can unleash its true strength.
Its materials
likely come from ancient times.
Even the Ancient God's memory doesn't recognize it.
I'll decide what to do with it another day.
Heaven Defying Bead...
3 months later
Only one last step
to become its master.
I, Wang Lin, began cultivating
thanks to this bead.
Back then, I left the Heng Yue Sect,
to risk seeking the Dao
and I almost died a hundred times.
I have waited 1000 years
to complete the Heaven Defying Bead.
This bead has accompanied me for far too long.
But I still
know very little about it.
After all those efforts,
Heaven Defying Bead,
let me see
what secrets you hide.
This big door...
What is it ?
Such a strong pressure !
This power doesn't come from a higher realm,
it's a shudder from the depths of my soul.
As if before this great door, we cultivators
can only shatter our Dao
and kneel in submission,
unable to resist.
The divide between mortal and immortal...
The divide between the heavens and the earth...
This kind of feeling
is something I haven't felt in a thousand years !
But my Dao
can't be shaken even by Gods and Demons.
That was 1000 years ago...
And today,
even more so !
Using a door to break my Dao...
You can dream on !
Heaven Defying Bead,
no matter what you are,
I'm the one who completed you !
If the heavens kill someone I care for,
I'll slaughter the heavens.
If you defy me,
then I will destroy your defiance !
The pressure has dissipated
and this giant arm has appeared once again.
But this arm isn't an Ancient God's.
Could it be a special restriction guarding the door ?
The Heaven Defying Bead was already full of mysteries
and now, it's even more mysterious.
I need to test it a bit more.
Go !
This is...
the power of laws !
If I try to advance by force,
I will be annihilated for sure.
Where does that giant door lead to ?
And what was that arm ?
The Heaven Defying Bead is complete,
an enormous opportunity is right before my eyes.
What did I do wrong ?
This is...
Thunder Pool\NSouthern Domain\NAllheaven Star System
The thunder energy in this pool
is far greater than that of the previous planet.
Even the Thunder Beast doesn't dare to go too deep.
Guard me from here.
Master,
such massive thunder energy...
I have no objections if you want to go in
but could you leave me outside ?
With my current physical body,
coming this far
is already the limit.
The thunder here is very strong.
It's an excellent place to practice the Thunder Origin Spell.
It will definitely allow me to refine origin energy.
Or maybe...
the Heaven Defying Bead guided me here
to use me to refine origin energy ?
Indeed !
Origin energy can help reopen the Heaven Defying Door.
The door reappeared
but I'm still no match for this giant arm.
Since Heaven Defying Bead has summoned the door again,
could it be that there is something
that can counter the giant arm in this place ?
Now or never !
Let me see what lies
behind this door !
Heaven Defying Space
Do you know
Who are you ?
what is the Dao ?
Do you know
or do you not ?
You don't know.
Then you are willing to seek the Dao.
The birth and destruction of planets,
the reincarnation cycle of all beings,
are all manifestations of the Dao.
It's enough
for one seeking the Dao in the morning
to die by the sunset.
Those seeking the Dao
only understand during death.
What a pity...
The power of the Life and Death reincarnation cycle is the Dao.
The cycle of karma is also the Dao.
That's all there is to it.
Mountains rise and fall,
stones know this.
Rivers flow to the sea,
water knows this.
The sun breaks through the clouds,
birds know this.
All of these things contain the Dao.
But unless you become that thing yourself,
you can't perceive its Dao.
The condensation and dissipation of planets
and the Life and Death reincarnation cycle are the Dao.
The peace of all beings and the cycle of karma are also the Dao.
But what causes them to rise ?
And what causes them to cease ?
Have you ever thought of that ?
All phenomena in the universe
originate from within oneself.
So this
is the Dao.
The goal of seeking the Dao
is to find yourself.
This silhouette...
Who is it ?
I've had my share of wounds,
now I want to fight back.
Is my destiny a wall of restrictions
that's blocking all my hopes
for life ?
My flesh and blood witnessed the past,
my adversity pushed me to brave the waves.
How do you navigate through the years passing by ?
Nirvana and rebirth are no longer
out of reach.
Immortals
are obsessed with delusions of grandeur.
Renegades
seek to crush the impermanence of the heavens.
Don't tell me that I overestimate myself
and that the path to revenge leads to hell
because I don't see the harm in that.
Returning to my body opened my eyes,
I need to continue my Immortal journey.
With a flick of a finger,
only my indomitable heart remains.
Life and death trials temper me, I am not afraid of losing my soul.
Even if there are countless tribulations and hardships.
Overcome this fate, smash through the obstacles,
like the descent of a god.
Returning to my body opened my eyes,
I need to continue my Immortal journey.
With a flick of a finger,
only my indomitable heart remains.
Life and death trials temper me, I am not afraid of losing my soul.
Even if there are countless tribulations and hardships.
Overcome this fate, smash through the obstacles,
like the descent of a god.
Ask
Qi Condensation
the perilous path filled with countless blades.
Foundation Establishment
Can the mundane world be shattered
Core Formation
Nascent Soul
by a child's steadfast heart ?
If the laws of this world
Soul Formation
Soul Transformation
stand in the way,
I'll defy the universe to tread the heavens
Ascendant
and ask this question to the sky.
My heart's deepest wish
is to not kneel before these mountains and rivers.
Don't accept your doomed fate,
karma can be changed.
Unwilling to let go,
my obsessions propel me forward.
Don't be afraid.
Thunder rumbles as I dare to tread through the reincarnation cycle.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.